Curiosity will lure you in...
The Tomb is a drama, horror, thriller film directed by Ulli Lommel.
Imprisoning a group of people in a living hell of darkness and
death the Puppetmaster controls the fate of each one.
One by one, the captives awake in agonizing pain—some are
slightly injured, others are fatally wounded.
The survivors are also mentally tortured by the unseen villain, who
demands that there can be only one winner at this game.
Tara Griffin, played by Victoria Ullmann.
Billy Tearford, played by Christian Behm.
Morris, played by Gerard Griesbaum.
Robert, played by Michael Barbour.
Dracy, played by Shawn Smith.
Dalida, played by Naidra Dawn Thomson.
HP Lovecraft's The Tomb is a 2007 American horror film directed by Ulli Lommel and starring
Victoria Ullmann, Christian Behm, Gerard Griesbaum, and Michael Barbour.
It is supposedly based on H.P.
Lovecraft's 1917 story, "The Tomb".
However, the plot of the film is completely
unrelated to the Lovecraft short story.
The film was compared to the 2004 film, Saw, and the
series was mentioned on the box art.
The film is also known simply as The Tomb, but the title on
the DVD case is HP Lovecraft's The Tomb.
However, on the film itself, the title is given as "H.P.
Lovecraft The Tomb", with no apostrophe or 's'.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.